KEEGAN SECK

OBJECTIVE

As a graduate of the UCSC Film and Digital Media degree program, I am well equipped for professional media production in any capacity. My education provides me with strong technical skills in film editing, where my experience with programs such as Adobe Premiere creates high-quality, professional content. Additionally, I worked in large teams to collaborate on complex film and live television projects, leading teams with my strong direction and organization skills. My long-term goal is to join a film or television production company to bring my powerful skill set and unique vision into the digial media age.

EDUCATION

Period	September 2012 — March 2017	
Degree	Bachelor of Arts in Film and Digital Media, Production Concentration	
University	University of California Santa Cruz	Santa Cruz, California

Experience

Period	April 2019 — August 2019	
	Production Intern	
Company	Contra Costa Television	Martinez, California
Period	September 2019 — March 2020	
Role	Production Assistant, Editor, Cameraman	
Сомрану	Contractor for Contra Costa Television	Martinez, California
Period	March 2021 — December 2021	
Role	Remote Video Editor Intern	
Сомрану	TomKin Consulting, LLC	West End, North Carolina

SKILLS

Writing	Developed strong writing abilities for film scripts and digital media projects. Proficient in technical and creative language, with effective use of feedback.
VIDEO	Experience with Adobe Creative Suite for televised and personal projects, ex-
Editing	ported in various codecs for the respective video platforms. Worked alongside
	and remotely with other students, clients, and co-workers to create profes-
	sional content.
Filmmaking	Hands-on experience or exposure to company owned audio and visual equip-
	ment for video productions and live broadcasts, including Canon XF cameras
	and NewTek TriCasters in studio and external settings.
Computer	Working skills with enterprise computer processes and services such as Mi-
Skills	crosoft Office software or Google Apps. Experience with programming lan-
	guages such as HTML, Java, and C++ with a large capacity for learning.
Organization	Years of experience working with complicated organizations and groups. Un-
	derstands effective group interaction and team management.